rvglobalsoft.com 2018-08-29

# 

## 1.Introduction

RVglobalsoft Company Ltd. Privacy Policy describes the treatment of information we (RVglobalsoft Co., Ltd. and its brands RVsitebuilder, RVskin, and RVssl) collect from and about you when you visit our websites (rvglobalsoft.com, and any of its subdomains, rvsitebuilder.com, rvskin.com, rvssl.com) or use our apps and other services that contain a link to this Privacy Policy or otherwise refer to or provide the URL to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”). Our Privacy Policy also describes other sources we use to obtain information about you; tells you how we use, share and protect your information; and what choices you have about how your information is used and shared. By using the Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner set out below.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at [privacy@rvglobalsoft.com](mailto:privacy@rvglobalsoft.com).

## 2\. What information do we collect?

###  We have two main persons we collect information: Visitors and Users.

  1. **Visitor:** the un-identified and non-identifiable information visitors wander our Services. We collect non-personal information which mainly consists of technical and aggregated usage information, such as ‘click’ activity on the Services, session and scrolls, non-identifying information regarding the device, operating system, internet browser, screen resolution, language and keyboard settings, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, etc.
  2. **User:** the individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable efforts cause the identification of an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature (“Personal Information”). We collect the Personal Information such as contact details; e-mail address, phone number, billing details; name, physical billing address, payment method and transaction details, details regarding a browsing or usage session (IP address, Geo-location and/or device unique identifier), details regarding connected third party accounts such as the e-mail or username for a connected PayPal, details of server (IP Address and access) and any other Personal Information provided to us through the access to and/or use of the Services. For the avoidance of doubt, any Non-personal Information that is connected or linked to Personal Information (for example, in order to improve the Services we offer) is deemed and treated by us as Personal Information, as long as such connection or linkage exists.

## 3.How do we use this information?

### We may use the Personal Information provided by you to:

  * To allow you to interact with us on our sites such as Support Center, Community posts and comments.
  * To provide you the Paid Services you purchase with us.
  * To send you the payment information and methods.
  * To keep track on troubleshoot progress you request.
  * To access to your server for troubleshooting.
  * To administer the internal operation such as troubleshooting, testing, data analysis, statistic and survey purposes.
  * To improve our website to have the effective content for you and well-displayed for your device.

## 4.Storage and Transfer of Data

All the information you provide may be processed and stored, transferred or accessed by our staffs for billing, support, technical troubleshooting, community purposes. We will take steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We have put in place technical and organisational procedures designed to safeguard the information we collected on this Site

### International transfers

Our sharing your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, may involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring, where required by law, at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

  * transferring personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission;
  * using specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe; or
  * transferring personal data to the United States to an entity if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US.

## 5.Cookies

### INFORMATION ABOUT OUR USE OF COOKIES AND TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Our Site uses cookies and other similar technologies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site, allows us to improve our Site and provide you with tailored content and advertising.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

## 6.How long we retain your data?

In general, we will retain your personal data as long as it is needed for the services and support. Personal Information may also be contained in backup files which we keep for information security purposes and regularly delete when the backup period is over. We will keep your Personal Information as long as you are holding active status with us, until you ask us to stop and erase it.

## 7.Your Right

  * You’re entitled to be informed that your Personal Information will be collected by us as explained above.
  * You’re entitled to ask for your Personal Information, support conversation, community posts and comments, to be exported for your use such as sending to other organisation.
  * You’re entitled to ask us to permanently remove your Personal Information, support conversation, community posts and comments from our company.

## 8.Contact Us

## RV Global Soft Co., Ltd.

### 1518/5, CeaShun Building, 3rd, 5th FL, Pracharaj 1 Rd., Wongsawang, Bang Sue, Bangkok, 10800. THAILAND.
